[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 49, "question": "All right, Mrs. Mensch, do you want to respond to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 50, "answer": "As I've just said, I made the claims in the select committee.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mrs. Mensch"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 61, "question": "What was it like for you being so close to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 62, "answer": "Well, it was -- it was very dramatic.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 77, "question": "Jonathan, what do we know about the attacker?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 78, "answer": "Well, right after the attack took place, I started speaking to the police who were running around.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Murdoch"]}, "docId": "110719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "RB", ",", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 92, "question": "How did they do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 93, "answer": "I think it -- miraculously, the pie may have saved the whole day for the Murdoch family.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 101, "question": "Would you agree with that, that it's the pie what won it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WP", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 102, "answer": "No, I actually don't think I would agree on that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "RB", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 110, "question": "And from what you saw, Richard, I mean, where would you say that the Murdochs were at their weakest today?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 111, "answer": "Clearly on the fundamental question which never got answered.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Richard"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 126, "question": "Have you had any reaction from the family since the end of the hearing today?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 127, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Rupert Murdoch"]}, "docId": "110719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "JJS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "IN", "JJS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 144, "question": "I mean is that a position that is acceptable for a guy who's chairman and CEO of News Corporation?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "NN", "CC", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 145, "answer": "I think it's quite a surprising position, and there is a difference between your reaction to this and I think that of most of the European public because most of us have never done business with Rupert Murdoch and know what he's like inside.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["CEO of News Corporation"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "RBS", "RB", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 160, "question": "Would you see it that way?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 161, "answer": "Yes, I most certainly would.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 165, "question": "And finally, Richard, I mean greatest scandal in British history from your experience?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 166, "answer": "Oh, no, no, no, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Richard"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 183, "question": "What does that mean?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 184, "answer": "Well, I tell a lot of stories in my standup act that, you know, or my points of view of different things.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 189, "question": "To put it mildly, haven't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 190, "answer": "Well, I think if you do standup, the kind of standup I like, you've got to tell the truth and you know hopefully you've had some interesting things.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 202, "question": "Is there anything about your life that you can't joke about?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 203, "answer": "Well, I can't think of anything.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", ":", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 232, "question": "Your weight, the way you look, everything?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 233, "answer": "My battle with food and my weight is the core of every -- of my alcoholism, of everything.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 236, "question": "And how are you feeling these days about the way you look?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 237, "answer": "I need to lose some weight.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Hormel"]}, "docId": "110719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 249, "question": "Did you remember that experience well?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 250, "answer": "I remember working at Hormel very well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 261, "question": "Were you a good hog slayer?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 262, "answer": "I was.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", ":", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", ":"], "qSentId": 271, "question": "ORGAN: What?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 272, "answer": "So -- yes, it was first --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mike", "Mo"], "LOCATION": ["Ottumwa", "Iowa"]}, "docId": "110719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ",", "NNP", ",", "CC", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 278, "question": "You did what?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 279, "answer": "Well, me, Mike, and Mo, who are still buddies of mine to this day, there's nothing to do in Ottumwa, Iowa, after 10:00.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "."], "qSentId": 296, "question": "What was that moment like?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 297, "answer": "Terrifying.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$15"], "LOCATION": ["University of Iowa"]}, "docId": "110719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "$", "CD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 315, "question": "When was the moment that you realized this could be a career and not just a bit of fun for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 316, "answer": "The first time I got offered a paying job, $15, I was in University of Iowa and I had some standup.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "PRP$", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "RB", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 330, "question": "I mean is that a good thing or not a good thing for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 331, "answer": "You know, but people have to understand, I haven't talked to her, you know, face to face in almost 18 years.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 357, "question": "And what would you say to her if she's watching?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP$", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 358, "answer": "I'd say good luck with your show.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "PRP$", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 362, "question": "Do you think she'll be pleased that you're happy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 363, "answer": "Part of her, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 393, "question": "Rather impressive remarks there I think, Tom, don't feel your old friend Arnold Schwarzenegger?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "NNS", "EX", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 394, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Arnold Schwarzenegger"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Austria"]}, "docId": "110719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "DT", ":", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", ":", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 407, "question": "What do you make of what's been going on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 408, "answer": "Well, you have to understand he grew up in a -- much like me in a small town in -- in Austria in his case.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 419, "question": "Were you -- were you as shocked as everybody else?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", ":", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 420, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 429, "question": "About what's been going on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "POS", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 430, "answer": "Well, we see each other.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "RBR", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 435, "question": "At what point can you crack a joke about this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 436, "answer": "Well, the only joke that I can crack is that he can no longer make fun of the women that I've been with.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 447, "question": "Is that a go, or is it -- but might it happen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", ":", "CC", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 448, "answer": "I think it's a go.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 452, "question": "You've been talking about it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 453, "answer": "Absolutely we've been talking about it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Arnold"]}, "docId": "110719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 462, "question": "The -- what kind of man is Arnold Schwarzenegger?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", ":", "WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 463, "answer": "I think Arnold is a great man.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Arnold Schwarzenegger"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 488, "question": "I mean, it's like a -- it's a torturous process, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 489, "answer": "It is torturous, and it's monotonous.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 501, "question": "You've made 100 movies?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 502, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "``", "JJ", "NNS", "''", ":"], "qSentId": 503, "question": "Which is your favorite?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 504, "answer": "Well, I mean, I loved \"True Lies\" --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 515, "question": "The one you don't like to talk about in civilized company?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "CD", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 516, "answer": "I think there was one.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "DT", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 565, "question": "-- at your worst, what are we talking in terms of consumption?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 566, "answer": "I was about a half ounce a day --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 567, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 568, "answer": "-- of cocaine.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 572, "question": "Did you remember how that made you feel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "IN", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 573, "answer": "Well, I will tell you this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 583, "question": "Do you -- do you drink at all now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 584, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 586, "question": "Literally nothing at all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 587, "answer": "Nothing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "RB", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 588, "question": "And do you ever get tempted?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 589, "answer": "I -- I watch people sometimes, normal people.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 609, "question": "Did you have any regrets about it, or is it something that happened to you, that you're just pleased you moved on that was for a long time probably quite a bit fun?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", ",", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 610, "answer": "I have regrets about the way I acted, you know, when I was using drugs and alcohol.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 619, "question": "How much of what went on then do you think determined how you became in your earlier adulthood?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "IN", "WP", "NN", "IN", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "JJR", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 620, "answer": "Well, relationships wise, if your mom leaves when you're four, you know, anything is possible.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 660, "question": "What did you do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 661, "answer": "I just -- I just said what I had to say.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 684, "question": "Did you hit him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 685, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 707, "question": "And did it bring you any kind of closure?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 708, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charlie"]}, "docId": "110719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 757, "question": "When you see someone like Charlie going through what he's been through the last few months, what's been your -- your view watching from afar?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBG", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP$", ":", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 758, "answer": "Well, you know, I love Charlie.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charlie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", ":", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 784, "question": "I mean, there in a nutshell is the immorality of Hollywood, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "EX", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 785, "answer": "That's the immorality of -- of everywhere.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Hollywood"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 803, "question": "What in the end made you stop?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 804, "answer": "I -- there was a night.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "VBG", ",", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 868, "question": "Have you managed to, despite all the partying and the extravagances and so on, have you retained enough to be pretty comfortable the rest of your life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", ",", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 869, "answer": "Well, if I'd have continued partying, obviously I wouldn't have anything.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]